The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Void
Thunder Celestial Realm
Spatial rifts !
Retreat !
The teleportation formation is far away
and the Thunder Celestial Realm is on the verge of collapse.
Dodging rifts like this
is too slow.
I refined this stamp with a tribulation.
It was even able to withstand a hit from Qing Shui
without collapsing.
Maybe...
It does work !
This stamp isn't affected by spatial rifts.
It's a decent speed.
I just need to focus my Divine Sense
on avoiding the giant spatial rifts 100 zhang in size.
He's using an entire Celestial Realm fragment as a vehicle ?
The fiend
is the only person in the world who can pull that off.
Senior !
Senior, save me !
Zhan Yun
Late stage Ascendant
(former Illusory Yin)
Zhan Family member
Senior, save me !
I'm...
I'm a member of the Zhan Family,
Zhan Konglie is my Senior Brother !
Her cultivation has dropped from Illusory Yin.
No wonder she's struggling.
This...
What kind of artifact is this ?
It can even destroy spatial rifts.
Junior's name is Zhan Yun.
Thank you for saving my life, Senior.
10 000 celestial jades
for saving your life.
Another 10 000
for every hour you stay here.
Here are 50 000 celestial jades,
please count them, Senior.
Xi Zifeng,
over here !
Come over here !
Xi Zifeng
Xi Family member
Late stage Ascendant
Zhan Yun ?
Wait for us !
Senior, please wait.
She is a friend of mine.
May I ask who this fellow cultivator is ?
Junior Xi Zifeng,
pays respects to Senior.
Thank you, Senior, for saving us at the Celestial Realm Gate earlier.
You saved our lives back then,
and saved us once again just now.
I will never forget
your kindness.
Zhou Zhou
Zhou Family member
Early stage Ascendant
I pay respects, Senior.
Do you have celestial jades ?
Where are we going ?
Senior said we're going
to the teleportation formation of the Thunder Celestial Temple.
But that teleportation formation
is only ever used by people of the Thunder Celestial Temple.
I trust Senior.
Look,
we aren't the only ones trusting him.
Wherever Senior goes,
is the only way out right now.
Give me a ride !
Wait for me !
We are headed to the Thunder Celestial Temple's teleportation formation.
Boarding requires a payment of celestial jades according to the rules:
10 000 to repay for saving your life
and then 10 000 per hour.
Next person !
I can finally catch my breath...
Hu Kailai
Corporeal Yang
Liu Wenying
It's Senior Hu !
He actually came too ?
We pay respects to Senior.
Here are my 1 200 000 celestial jades,
to thank Senior for permitting me to accompany you.
Stay close !
The path behind the stamp
has fewer rifts !
Master ?
Shengong Hu
pays respects to Master.
Sit down.
Did...
Did he just call him...
Master ?
The teleportation formation is to the northwest.
If Master wishes to go,
there's a shortcut here.
You're a member of the Thunder Celestial Temple.
I intend to force my way through the Thunder Celestial Temple's teleportation formation.
Have you considered the consequences
of following me ?
I have.
The Thunder Celestial Temple showed me kindness.
But since I offered you my Dao Soul,
they've ostracized me.
I will always remember
how Master guided me back then.
In this battle...
Disguise yourself
and hide your aura.
If we fight today,
you're not allowed to act.
Understood !
Master,
there are even more rifts ahead.
Some are more than 100 zhang in size.
I received warnings from the Thunder Celestial Temple
via communication jades.
Got it.
Zhan Yun !
Zhan Yun,
hold tight !
Almost there...
Teleportation formation
of the Thunder Celestial Temple
Thunder Celestial Realm
Messenger Liao,
I'm going ahead.
We'll see each other at the Temple soon.
Liao Yan
Rank 2 Thunder Celestial Messenger
Corporeal Yang
Senior Liao,
most of us
have withdrawn by now, right ?
In an incense stick of time,
the teleportation formation will open again
and we will leave.
Before leaving,
we'll destroy the formation.
The Thunder Celestial Temple is a forbidden area,
we don't allow lowly cultivators inside.
Understood !
Some of them really aren't scared of death...
My lords,
please understand us
and give us a way out.
Scram !
Charging your way here
is already a capital offense !
Today, you shall die alongside the Celestial Realm.
Consider it a lavish funeral.
Master !
Sit down !
Heavenly
Chop !
Overestimating yourself ?
Help me if you don't want to die !
Channel origin energy towards Senior !
8 Corporeal Yang cultivators are holding this position.
You're just a bunch of trash.
The strongest among you
are merely 3 Early stage Corporeal Yang.
The rest of you are
Ascendant
and Illusory Yin.
And you dare to call yourselves cultivators ?
You're just a bunch of lowly rogue cultivators.
Today
is the day you meet your end !
All Messengers, heed my order !
Kill these bandits
to earn some merit !
Attack me together !
Lock the origin, seal the soul !
You bunch of Ascendants
are just ants trying to shake a tree !
If you won't let us live,
then none of you will live either !
Kill !
This is going too far !
Intolerable !
Go to hell !
Fight them with everything !
Charge !
At this rate...
we'll end up buried with them !
Out of all the beliefs in the world,
the struggle to survive
is the only one nothing can stop !
Make way !
He's only Corporeal Yang...
Just how many of his peers has he killed
to have such an intense killing intent ?
Activate the formation !
Go !
Quick, follow them.
Too late !
Destroy the formation !
No !
Since you messed with us like this...
Don't blame me for our mutual destruction.
Heavenly
Chop !
The teleportation formation is destroyed...
We can't leave anymore !
My Li Family's restrictions
can restore this dead formation.
By crudely patching it with celestial restrictions,
it can be activated one final time.
We will never forget your great kindness !
May I ask Senior's name ?
Xu Mu
Senior Xu,
we will never forget
your great kindness !
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
by a child's steadfast heart ?
Nascent Soul
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
stand in the way,
Soul Transformation
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
Ascendant
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.